Hi there. So first you need to
be on the Amazon AWS console. Once you're there,
sign in with your
root user.
You can sign in from here.
And you need to do a root user sign in. Okay?
This is a root user sign in that you're doing.
Here, it should be chosen as root user.
Then you can add your email and password,
and sign in.
Once you've signed in, you can see this at the
right top side. You can click on your profile, and
here you will be able to see Upgrading your plan. Okay?
This option you need to
click.
You'll be able to see this page to upgrade. You can click on Upgrade plan.
Your account is now upgraded successfully. You can click on Continue.
And here's your account has been successfully upgraded.
You can see this when you click again on this profile.
This is how you will be able to see.
Just okay?